# ARIANA RODRÍGUEZ

Front end developer | Email & Interactive Developer



Cel: 72057266



ariiana1d@gmail.com



San Rafael, Heredia



https://www.linkedin.com/in/arianarodriguez-38a362116/

#### ABOUT ME

More than 4 years' experience as a developer. I'm interested in creating content and am always open to new ideas and challenges. I'm passionate about having new experiences that allow me to develop both personally and professionally.

#### EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

**CTP Mercedes Norte (2014 - 2016)** 

• Technician in Business Informatic

Intensa Institute (2018 - 2020)

English

# Build Responsive Real-World Websites with HTML and CSS

Udemy, 2024.

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-66633d72-a5f1-4122-a4d6-d126317c8a90/

#### **Develop Websites and Components using AEM**

Adobe Learning, 2024.

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ariana-rodriguez-38a362116/details/certifications/1705093698043/single-media-viewer/?profileId=ACoAABzieZoBjxKLT3lollp-xOudS0i5V3s3goo

#### Politécnico Internacional (2017 - 2018)

background-size: 100

late(-50%,

la(0, 0, 0

• Web development technician

#### **Universidad Fidelitas (2022 - currently)**

• Bachelor's degree in computer systems engineer.

#### **Author and Manage Pages Using AEM Sites I**

Adobe Learning, 2024.

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ariana-rodriguez-38a362116/details/certifications/1705093698043/single-media-viewer/?profileId=ACoAABzieZoBjxKLT3IoIlp-xOudS0i5V3s3goo

#### **Author and Manage Pages Using AEM Sites II**

Adobe Learning, 2024.

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ariana-rodriguez-38a362116/details/certifications/1712541941241/single-media-viewer/?profileId=ACoAABzieZoBjxKLT3lollp-xOudS0i5V3s3goo

#### EXPERIENCE

#### **IT Intership**

#### CoopeCaja CR, 3weeks in 2015

 IT support tasks to the equipment required (Desktops, laptops, printers) and handle of Databases with MySQL.

#### **Creative Email Engineer**

#### Prodigious LATAM, March 2018 - Agust 2020

I was responsible for make some tasks like as:

- Emails code with HTML, CSS.
- Responsive Emails.
- Content management work with Oracle Responsys.
- Deployment of the Email campaigns.
- · Checklist and Peer review.
- Basic SQL statements.
- Email on Acid tool.
- Basic JavaScript for Email with dynamic content.

#### **Email developer**

#### Prose on Pixels, December 2020 - June 2024

I was worked as email developer beside I worked in projects about interactive and front-end developer, I was responsible to make the follow tasks:

- Development of HTML5 Emails following best practices
- Development of JavaScript banners using the GSAP library:

Creating interactive and animated ads that meet industry standards.

- Development of applications and websites with Angular, Electron JS, Capacitor, Jekyll: Implementing efficient and scalable front-end solutions.
- Experience with Adobe AEM: Managing and developing content using Adobe Experience Manager.

#### **IT Professional Practice**

#### Allergan inc, september 2016 - December 2016

 IT support tasks to the equipment required (Desktops, laptops, printers) also some networking tasks

## Freelance IT Technician Colegio Deportivo de Santo Domingo, March 2021 - November 2023

I was worked as IT technician doing the follow tasks:

- Preventive computers and printers maintenance.
- Networking tasks.
- Logo design.

### Freelance Developer Cloud Forest Studio, April 2022 - Currently working

I've been working as developer doing the follow tasks:

- Building HTML5 responsive emails.
- Building animate and static banners with CSS, HTML and Gsap JS.
- Content managament for banners on Google DoubleClick Studio.

# • LANGUAGES AND SKILLS

